<resources>
    // Home Page
    <string name="app_name">Recycling Academy</string>
    <string name="intro_name">Recycling Academy</string>
    <string name="aboutUs">About Us</string>
    <string name="importance">Importance of Recycling</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="recycle">Recycle Categories</string>
    <string name="references">References</string>
    <string name="plastic">Plastic</string>
    <string name="paper">Paper</string>
    <string name="glass">Glass</string>
    <string name="metal">Metal</string>
    // About Us Page
    <string name="logoImageDescription">The logo of the Massachusetts Academy of Math and Science
    </string>
    <string name="aboutRecyclingRaccoonsHeader">Who are the Recycling Raccoons?</string>
    <string name="aboutRecyclingRaccoonsDescription">We are a team of students from the
        Massachusetts Academy of Math and Science in Worcester, Massachusetts who strive to help our
        community through the creation of this app. As concerns for the environment grow, proper
        recycling becomes increasingly important. In our research, we found that people that do not
        recycle do so due to a lack of access or because they find recycling tedious or confusing.
        Hearing this, we decided that it would be helpful to simplify the most confusing part of
        the process—determining recyclability or reusing recyclable items. With the guide of this
        app, everyone becomes capable of helping to save the environment.</string>
    <string name="aboutMAMSHeader">What is Mass Academy?</string>
    <string name="aboutMAMSDescription">The Massachusetts Academy of Math and Science (MAMS) is a
        public school in Worcester, Massachusetts that offers STEM-focused (Science, Technology,
        Engineering, Math) courses at an advanced level for 11th and 12th graders. The school puts
        an emphasis on project-based learning and collaboration. Students also pursue long-term
        projects such as a 5-month independent research project, a 3-month assistive device group
        project, and a 2-month Apps for Good group project. This app is the work of one Apps for
        Good project that provides the community with assistance during the recycling process.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutAFGHeader">What is Apps for Good?</string>
    <string name="aboutAFGDescription">Apps for Good is an organization that brings education and
        access to students interested in coding all over the world. The learning experience is
        student-driven as small groups of students work together to learn and create their own app
        which makes a difference in their community. This app is the product of the Recycling
        Raccoon’s Apps for Good project.</string>
    // Recycling Categories
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="recyclingCategoryIntroduction">Please Select a Recycling Category</string>
    <string name="plasticCategory">Plastic</string>
    <string name="plasticCategoryCD">Plastic Bottle</string>
    <string name="paperCategory">Paper</string>
    <string name="paperCategoryCD">Cardboard Box</string>
    <string name="glassCategory">Glass</string>
    <string name="glassCategoryCD">Glass Cup</string>
    <string name="metalCategory">Metal</string>
    <string name="metalCategoryCD">Metal Bars</string>

    <string name="recyclingImportance">Recycling Importance</string>
    <string name="landfill">Landfills</string>
    <string name="incinerator">Incinerator</string>
    <string name="resources">Resources</string>
    <string name="energy">Energy</string>
    <string name="landfill_info">This is a test</string>
</resources>